final List<Map<String, dynamic>> grammarQuizQuestions = [
  {
    'question': 'I ___ a student.\nأنا طالب.',
    'answers': ['is', 'am', 'are'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'She ___ happy.\nهي سعيدة.',
    'answers': ['am', 'are', 'is'],
    'correct': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'They ___ friends.\nهم أصدقاء.',
    'answers': ['am', 'are', 'is'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'He ___ a teacher.\nهو مُعلم.',
    'answers': ['is', 'are', 'am'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'We ___ from Egypt.\nنحن من مصر.',
    'answers': ['are', 'is', 'am'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'You ___ my best friend.\nأنت صديقي المفضل.',
    'answers': ['am', 'is', 'are'],
    'correct': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'It ___ a cat.\nإنها قطة.',
    'answers': ['are', 'is', 'am'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'I ___ not sad.\nأنا لست حزينًا.',
    'answers': ['are', 'am', 'is'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'She ___ not a doctor.\nهي ليست طبيبة.',
    'answers': ['is', 'are', 'am'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'They ___ not at home.\nهم ليسوا في المنزل.',
    'answers': ['am', 'are', 'is'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
];
